Don't turn her on.
Subservience is a science fiction, horror, thriller film directed by SK Dale.
With his wife out sick, a struggling father brings home a lifelike AI, only to have
his self-aware new help want everything her new family has to offer...
Like the affection of her owner and she'll kill to get it.
Alice, played by Megan Fox.
Nick, played by Michele Morrone.
Maggie, played by Madeline Zima.
Isla, played by Matilda Firth.
Monty, played by Andrew Whipp.
Lewis, played by Atanas Srebrev.
Subservience is a 2024 American science fiction thriller film directed by S.K.
Dale from a screenplay by Will Honley and April Maguire.
It stars Megan Fox as an artificially intelligent gynoid who gains sentience
and becomes hostile, and Michele Morrone as her purchaser.
The film also stars Madeline Zima, Matilda Firth, Jude
Allen Greenstein, and Andrew Whipp.
Subservience was theatrically released in the United
States by XYZ Films on September 13, 2024.
The film received generally mixed reviews from critics and had grossed $264,096.
The film explores themes of artificial intelligence
(a.i.), robot, suspenseful, tense, intense.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking and intense.